buymeonce.com 2019-08-11

# Privacy Policy | BuyMeOnce

## Introduction

BuyMeOnce found at https://buymeonce.com/ (“Website” or “we”) is governed by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used. This statement only applies to this Website.

Any personal data about our users (the “User” or “you”) provided to or gathered by the Services is controlled by BuyMeOnce (a company incorporated in the United States of America with a registered office at ExportAction LLC, 4500 140th Avenue North, Suite 101, Clearwater, FL 33762).

## Contents

  1. What Does This Policy Cover?
  2. What Personal Information Does the Website Collect?
  3. How Do We Collect Information on our Users?
    1. Personal Data You Provide to Us
    2. Personal Data Collected Automatically
    3. E-mail Communications
  4. What About Cookies?
  5. Why Do We Collect Information?
  6. Sharing Information With Third Parties
    1. Partner Affiliate Websites We Do Not Control
    2. Partner Drop-shipping Websites
    3. Shopify Integrated Checkout
    4. PayPal Integrated Checkout
    5. Other Third Parties
    6. User Profiles and Other Information You Post Publicly
    7. Business Transfers
    8. Protection of the Website and Others and a Transfer in the Ownership of the Website
    9. With Your Consent
  7. Is Personal Information About Me Secure?
  8. What Personal Data Can I Access?
  9. What About Links To Third Party Websites?
  10. Data Retention
  11. What Choices Do I Have?
  12. Children
  13. Changes to This Policy
  14. Questions or Concerns

## 1\. What does this Policy cover?

This policy covers the Website’s treatment of personal data that the Website gathers when you access the Services and/or use the Content. We explain what information we gather, why we gather it and the choices you have regarding your personal information.

## 2\. What Personal Information does the Website collect?

We may collect two types of data and information from you:

The first type of information is non-identifiable and anonymous information (“Non-personal information”). We are not aware of the identity of the User from which we have collected Non-Personal Information. Non-Personal Information is any unconcealed information which is available to us while Users are using the Sites. Non-personal Information which is being gathered consists of technical information and behavioural information, including, but not limited to, the operating system, type of browser, screen resolution, the period of time the User visited the Site, etc.

The second type of information is individually identifiable information (“Personal Information”). This information may identify an individual or may be of a private and/or sensitive nature. Personal information which is being gathered consists of any personal details provided consciously and voluntarily by the User including name, email, address, IP address and other unique identifiers and any other information you choose to provide to the Website.

As customers, you do not have any legal obligation to provide any information to the Website. However, we require certain information from you in order to operate properly, including completing a transaction on your behalf. Login credentials (email and username) enable us to personalize and improve our services. You hereby agree and acknowledge that any Personal Information you do provide to us is provided at your own free will, for the purposes mentioned in this Privacy Notice and that we may keep such Personal Information in a database(s) which will be registered and kept in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We retain personal information no longer than is legally permissible and delete personal information when it is no longer necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.

## 3\. How do we collect information on our Users?

**3.1. Personal Data You Provide to Us**

We collect Personal Information when you register and open an account with the Website by completing the registration form. We receive and store any information you enter on the Services or provide to us in any other way. The types of personal data collected may include your full name, email address, IP address, browser information, username, password, home and billing address, shipping address, credit card information and any other information necessary for us to provide the Services, including the usernames and passwords for your accounts and profiles on third-party sites with which the Services interoperates.

We will collect details of transactions you carry out through our Services and of the fulfilment of your orders. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features (see section 9 below for further information on the choices you have).

**3.2. Personal Data Collected Automatically**

a. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Sites or use another feature of our Service. In other words, when you are using the Sites we are aware of it and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage, either independently or through the help of third-party services as detailed below. The Website automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, certain cookie information (see Section 4 below for more information on Cookie usage) and the page you requested.

b. More generally, our Services automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Services and its components. The Website only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Services or another feature of the Content so that we can make the Services appealing to as many customers as possible and improve the Content. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers use our Content. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use our Content, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. Again, the Website never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally, unless it needs to in order to complete a transaction on your behalf. The Website only discloses information to third parties it trusts.

**3.3. E-mail Communications**

We often receive a confirmation when you open an email from the Website if your computer supports this type of program. The Website uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful.

Depending on your email notification settings, we may send you instant or weekly blog post updates, weekly product recommendations and other marketing emails that include new products or discounts you may be interested in. You can choose to stop getting these updates at any time by opting out for promotional emails using the unsubscribe link in the emails, updating your account settings or through other settings we may provide for this purpose.

## 4\. What About Cookies?

The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies, by the Website, by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our Website may be entirely usable.

## 5\. Why Do We Collect Information?

Non-personal Information is collected in order to:

  * Create aggregated statistical data for research purposes and customisation and improvement of the Sites

Personal Information is collected in order to:

  * Operate the Services
  * Process payments
  * Communicate with you about your orders, as well as products, services and promotional offers
  * Administer your accounts and update our records
  * Improve our Services and platform, prevent or detect abuses of our Services and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf
  * Be able to contact you for the purpose of providing technical assistance, sale reminders and other related information to the Services and collect feedback
  * For market research, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity
  * To provide to third-party contractors
  * For risk control, for fraud detection and prevention, to comply with laws and regulations, and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements
  * To enforce the Website's Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy

## 6\. Sharing Information With Third Parties

We share your Personal Information only as described in this policy and require commercial entities with which we share your Personal Information to agree to keep your information confidential.

**6.1. Partner Affiliate Websites We Do Not Control**

The Website works with a variety of merchants (“Affiliate Partners”) in order to offer you the widest possible choice of items through the Services. We promote and sell the items offered by the Affiliate Partners through the Services. When you choose to buy an item, you will be taken directly to their online store. You can easily recognise when a third-party business is associated with your transaction, and we will share your personal data that is related to such transactions with that business. Please note that: (i) the third-party business will use and share your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy; (ii) you should check its policy before completing any transaction involving such third-party business; and (iii) such third-party business is solely responsible for its use and sharing of your personal data.

The Website currently works with the following Affiliate Partners:

**USA Affiliate Partner**

| 

**Privacy Policy**  
  
---|---  
  
Avant Link

| 

https://www.avantlink.com/privacy  
  
Amazon | 

https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=ap_footer_privacy_notice?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496&pop-up=1  
  
Awin

| 

https://www.awin.com/gb/legal/privacy-policy  
  
iDevAffiliate

| 

https://www.idevdirect.com/policies.php  
  
Pepperjam

| 

https://www.pepperjam.com/legal#privacy  
  
Performance Horizon

| 

https://performancehorizon.com/privacy-policy  
  
Rakuten

| 

https://rakutenmarketing.com/en-uk/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy  
  
Refersion

| 

https://www.refersion.com/privacy  
  
Shareasale

| 

https://www.shareasale.com/PrivacyPolicy.pdf  
  
SunGod

| 

https://www.sungod.co/privacy  
  
Webgains

| 

http://www.webgains.com/public/en/privacy/  
  
Flex Offers | https://flex.com/privacy-policy  
Target | https://www.target.com/c/target-privacy-policy/-/N-4sr7p  
WalkYourDogWithLove | https://walkyourdogwithlove.com/terms.html  
Zojila | https://zojila.com/privacy-policy  
  
At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other Affiliate Partners. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Note: BuyMeOnce is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

**6.2. Partner Drop-shipping Websites**

The Website works with selected merchants (“Drop-shipping Partners”) in order to offer you the best user experience through our Services. We promote and sell the items offered by the Drop-shipping Partners through the Services. When you choose to buy an item, you will be taken to our Integrated Checkout to perform the transaction. The Personal Information you provide through the Integrated Checkout will be shared with the Drop-Shipping Partners in order to complete the transaction and to send you email notifications regarding your order. Please note that: (i) the Drop-shipping Partner will use and share your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy; (ii) you should check its policy before completing any transaction involving a Drop-shipping Partner; and (iii) the Drop-shipping Partner is solely responsible for its use and sharing of your personal data.

The Website currently works with the following Drop-shipping Partners:

**USA Drop-shipping Partner**

| 

**Privacy Policy**  
  
---|---  
Ally Bee | https://ally-bee.com/pages/privacy-policy  
AmaElla  | https://www.amaella.com/terms-conditions/  
Black Horse Lane | https://blackhorselane.com/privacy-policy/  
Bulldog Tools (Clarington Forge) | https://www.claringtonforge.com/privacy-policy  
Chan and Krys | https://chanandkrys.com/privacy  
Citizen's Mark | https://citizensmark.com/pages/privacy-policy  
Chrysmela | https://chrysme.la/pages/privacy-policy  
Coyuchi | https://www.coyuchi.com/privacy-policy.html  
Davy J | Not available  
Dehen 1920 | https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/24526038  
Duluth Pack | https://www.duluthpack.com/privacy-policy  
Earlywood Designs | https://www.earlywooddesigns.com/pages/faq  
  
Elvis & Kresse

| 

https://www.elvisandkresse.com/pages/privacy-policy  
  
Finex | https://finexusa.com/privacy/  
  
Finlayson

| 

https://www.finlayson.fi/pages/tietosuojaseloste  
  
Flowfold | https://www.flowfold.com/pages/privacy-policy  
GIR  | https://gir.co/privacy-policy  
GroFive | https://grofive.com/pages/privacy-policy  
K.A.N Bags |  Not Available  
Lemuel MC | https://www.lemuelmc.com/termsandconditions  
  
Liberty Flatware

| 

https://www.libertytabletop.com/privacy-policy/  
  
little miss workbench | Not Available  
Lowie | https://ilovelowie.com/pages/our-privacy-policy  
  
Luks Linen

| 

https://lukslinen.com/pages/privacy-policy  
  
Maxwell Scott |  ttps://www.maxwellscottbags.com/leather/privacy-policy/  
Midnight Scoop | Not Available  
Minirig | https://minirigs.co.uk/minirigs-privacy-policy  
Muddy Puddles | https://www.muddypuddlesproject.org/privacy-policy/  
The New Blak |  Not Available  
Olen Organic | https://www.olenorganic.com/pages/privacy-policy  
Origin Utensils |  Not Available  
Organic Basics |  https://www.organicbasics.com/pages/privacypolicy  
OrganiCup | https://www.organicup.com/privacy-policy/  
Pebble | http://kahiniwalla.com/shop/privacy-policy  
Plaine Products | https://www.plaineproducts.com/privacy-policy/  
Plumen | https://plumen.com/privacy-policy-2/  
Readerest | https://www.readerest.com/pages/privacy-policy  
  
Richmond Kettle Company

| 

https://www.richmondkettlecompany.com/privacy-policy/?v=79cba1185463  
  
Risdon & Risdon

| 

Not Available  
  
Rockwell Razors | https://getrockwell.com/pages/privacy-policy  
  
SoMo

| 

https://somolondon.com/pages/terms-privacy  
  
Starseeds

| 

https://starseeds.eco/pages/privacy-policy  
  
Swedish Stockings

| 

https://en.swedishstockings.com/pages/privacy-policy  
  
Thomas Clipper  | https://thomasclipper.com/pages/privacy-policy  
  
The White T-Shirt Company

| 

https://www.thewhitetshirt.com/terms-and-conditions  
  
Wishbone Design Studio | http://wishbonedesign.com/#!/contact/privacy/  
  
At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other Drop-shipping Partners. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

The Website requires our Drop-shipping Partners to honour your opt-out requests if you elect to stop receiving marketing emails. Please be advised that you cannot opt-out of receiving emails related to your transactions. If, for whatever reason, your opt-out request is not honoured, please let us know and we will attempt to resolve the issue.

The Website may also share your data with the Drop-shipping Partners in connection with certain promotions and competitions. These will be subject to additional rules and conditions which will be made available at the time of any such competition or promotion. You should carefully review the rules and conditions relating to such competitions and promotions.

**6.3. Shopify Integrated Checkout**

For payments made on the Website via our Integrated Checkout, we use a process provider called Shopify. Please note that we will share your personal data with Shopify that is related to such transactions and Shopify may collect personal data from you directly via cookies or other means in order to process such transactions. Your transaction with Shopify is subject to Shopify’s terms and conditions. Information you share with Shopify through our Integrated Checkout is subject to Shopify’s terms and conditions as well as their Privacy Policy, [which is available here.](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy) By using the Services and making payments through the Services, you are agreeing to Shopify's use of your personal data in accordance with their privacy policy.

**6.4. PayPal Integrated Checkout**

For payments made on the Website via our Integrated Checkout, we offer the use of PayPal’s payment services via an account connection. When you authorise the connection, the Website will exchange your Personal data and other information directly with PayPal to perform the transaction. Information you share with PayPal through our Integrated Checkout is subject to PayPal’s terms and conditions as well as their Privacy Policy, [which you can view here.](https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) By using the Services and making payments through PayPal via our Services, you are agreeing to PayPal’s use of your personal data in accordance with their privacy policy.

**6.5. Other Third Parties**

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information. Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

**Third-Party Service or App**

| 

**What Personal Information it Collects and What the Information is Used for**

| 

**Privacy Policy**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Google Analytics

| 

IP address; used for tracking Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website

| 

https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en  
  
MailChimp

| 

Name, email address; used for delivery of email updates, newsletters and email marketing

| 

https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/  
  
Feefo Ratings & Reviews

| 

Name, email address, purchase history, transaction history; used for delivery of product and service review requests

| 

https://www.feefo.com/business/gb_en/privacy-policy  
  
Facebook Pixel

| 

IP address; provides information about how users are responding to Facebook ads

| 

https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation  
  
ESC Custom Contact Forms (Shopify App)

| 

Name, email address; used for collecting and answering customer contact form emails

| 

https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy  
  
Geolocation Redirect (Shopify App)

| 

IP address; used direct users to the correct website services available in their country

| 

https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy  
  
At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

**6.6. User Profiles and Other Information You Post Publicly**

User profile information including your username, name, email address, and other information you enter (“User Submissions”) may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services. Any personal data or content that you voluntarily disclose online (in comment areas, etc.) become publicly available and can be viewed, collected and used by others. Any images, captions, physical descriptions, personal interests or other content that you submit to the Services may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels and may be viewed by the general public.

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post information to public areas on the Services or any other public forums, such information can be accessed by the public.

**6.7. Business Transfers**

If the Website, or substantially all of its assets were acquired in the unlikely event that the Website goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of the Website may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

**6.8. Protection of the Website and Others and a Transfer in the Ownership of the Website**

We may release personal data when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law, regulation or legal request; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of the Website, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. You agree that we may also share your data with entities where the Website is engaged in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this policy.

**6.9. With Your Consent**

By using the Services, you consent to our sharing of personal data for the above purposes.

For the avoidance of doubt, the Website may transfer and disclose Non-personal information to third parties at its own discretion.

## 7\. Is Personal Information About Me Secure?

The personal data in the Website account you have with us is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure that there is no unauthorised access to your account and personal data by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. You are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the Services and for any activities or actions under your password. The Website encourages you to use “strong” passwords (passwords that use a combination of upper and lower case letters, numbers and symbols) with your account. The Website cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with the above requirements.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. The Website endeavors to protect personal data but we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Services. Unauthorised entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, the Website cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our platform; any transmission of data is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## 8\. What About Links To Third Party Websites?

The Services contain links to other sites. The Website is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This policy only governs information collected on the Services.

We will take care to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided us with. We encrypt your information to protect it from unauthorised use. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third-party business partners to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal data.

To help ensure that your shopping experience is safe, simple and secure, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

## 9\. What Personal Data Can I Access?

The Website allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information: your name; user email address; telephone number; username and password; profile picture; bio; website; user preferences and notification; zip- and/or post-codes, billing address, and payment information.

The information you can access will change as the Services change. If you are a registered user of the Website, you can change or delete any saved payment card details and add or edit shipping and billing address information.

In the UK, the General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR") gives you the right to access information held about you. For any request or question regarding obtaining a copy of personal data we hold relating to you, and/or correction or deletion of your personal data, and/or object to any processing of your personal data, you can submit a Subject Access Request by emailing us at contact@buymeonce.com. We will respond to your access and/or correction request within 30 days.

However, please note that although your Personal Information may be removed from our databases, the Website will retain the anonymous information contained in the data you provided, and such information will continue to be used by us for statistical purpose.

## 10\. Data Retention

After a request from a User to delete any data, an automated process will begin that permanently deletes the relevant data. Once begun, this process cannot be reversed and data will be permanently deleted. Any data which is not deleted shall be kept in an anonymized manner.

As a registered User you can always view, access, change and delete your information by logging into your account.

Similarly, the Website collects and retains usage data, other metadata and statistical information concerning the use of the Service are not subject to the deletion procedures in this Notice and may be retained by the Website. Some data may be retained also on our third party service providers’ servers.

## 11\. What Choices Do I Have?

As set out above, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of the Services.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in section 10. “What Personal Data Can I Access” above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

Once the Website accounts are activated, you may request deletion of your account by following the instructions at the Account Settings section of the Services. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

When you register for an account at our Services, you consent to receive certain email or other communications from us; if you do not wish to receive any such communications, you should not register for an account at our Services. We may also use your data to provide you with information about products and services which may be of interest to you, directly or on behalf of one of our business partners. You can, however, change the type and frequency of the emails you receive from us at any time by changing your email settings or by unsubscribing from such emails.

Most mobile devices provide users with the ability to disable location services. These controls are usually located in the device's settings menu. Please contact your mobile service carrier or device manufacturer if you have questions about how to disable your device's location services.

Please note that if you choose not to receive legal notices from us, such as this policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

## 12\. Children

We do not knowingly market or sell products for purchase by children. The Services are not designed for use by children under 13 years old. Children under 13 are not allowed to register with or use the Services or submit personal data through the Services. We do not knowingly collect personal data from anyone under the age of 13. If we discover that we have collected personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information immediately.

## 13\. Changes To This Policy

The Website reserves the right to change this Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make substantial changes in the way we use personal data, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Services or sending you an email. Otherwise, all other changes to this Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the Website and/or Services after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

## 14\. Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Services or the Content, [please send us a detailed message here](https://buymeonce.com/pages/contact). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. If your questions or concerns are not answered online, you may write to us at BuyMeOnce ℅ ExportAction LLC, 4500 140th Avenue North, Suite 101, Clearwater, FL 33762.

This Agreement has been drawn up in the English language. In case of discrepancies between the English text version of this Agreement and any translation, the English version shall prevail.

 **Last Revised: 05 June 2018**
